<resources>
    <string name="app_name">JohnBoysTips</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="about_text">

        I want people to have access to my Tips and that\'s it. I don\'t want to charge extortionate amounts each month for you to have the privilege to bet on my Tips.
        I don\'t want to make people have to bet via my bookmakers. I don\'t want to charge you a commission for you to gamble your money on my Tips.

        \n\nAll I\'m going to do is charge you £9.99 a month and you can bet on all my Tips or just one!

        \n\nThere are no catches no hidden charges. You are just going to get access to my 30 years of horse knowledge!

        \n\nYou\'re asking why&#8230; well for nearly a year now I\'ve been giving these Tips away for free on my Twitter account and this can be proven by looking at @Lordgimack and checking my form out.

        \n\nMy stats speak for themselves I have got over 72%  of all my bets correct and that\'s pretty impressive. And now I want to share it with a wider audience.
        With my new website and App I want to really show the racing world what I know.

        \n\nYou can start and finish whenever you want so there is no yearly subscription only a monthly one.

        \n\nAll the best and remember

        \n\n"We don\'t need luck"

    </string>

    <string name="bio_text">

        As an 11 year old in 1986 my first bet was placed on my behalf by my dad. West Tip won the Grand National and I was delighted. I have been engrossed in the Sport of Kings ever since.

        \n\nStarting off at Yarmouth then onto Newmarket and Epsom the Flat Classics were my earliest successes, Commander in Chief, Oath, Galileo, Lammtara, Sakhee, George Washington and Sir Percy were memorable.

        \n\nAt the turn of the century National Hunt especially the Festival and Irish Racing gripped me with the passion and adrenalin.

        \n\nBest Mate, Denman, Kauto Star, Long Run, Synchronised, Hurricane Fly and now Vautour are my highlights.

        \n\nFor the past few years I have used Twitter to post daily my personal selections which have proved popular and profitable.

        \n\nMy principle is simple. Provide fellow punters with quality not quantity selections that I back myself avoiding the lottery of sand concentrating on the turf.

    </string>

</resources>
